[
    {
        "question": "What is the temperature/weather today(04-08-2024) in Nairobi?",
        "answer": "The weather today (04-08-2024) in Nairobi will see a low of 16.13\u00b0C and a high of 16.13\u00b0C, with overcast clouds. The average temperature is 16.13\u00b0C. Morning temperature is 16.13\u00b0C, evening temperature is 16.13\u00b0C, and night temperature is 16.13\u00b0C."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temperature/weather today(04-08-2024) in Bungoma?",
        "answer": "The weather today (04-08-2024) in Bungoma will see a low of 15.75\u00b0C and a high of 15.75\u00b0C, with broken clouds. The average temperature is 15.75\u00b0C. Morning temperature is 15.75\u00b0C, evening temperature is 15.75\u00b0C, and night temperature is 15.75\u00b0C."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temperature/weather today(04-08-2024) in Kisii?",
        "answer": "The weather today (04-08-2024) in Kisii will see a low of 13.53\u00b0C and a high of 13.53\u00b0C, with broken clouds. The average temperature is 13.53\u00b0C. Morning temperature is 13.53\u00b0C, evening temperature is 13.53\u00b0C, and night temperature is 13.53\u00b0C."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temperature/weather today(04-08-2024) in Eldoret?",
        "answer": "The weather today (04-08-2024) in Eldoret will see a low of 14.16\u00b0C and a high of 14.16\u00b0C, with clear sky. The average temperature is 14.16\u00b0C. Morning temperature is 14.16\u00b0C, evening temperature is 14.16\u00b0C, and night temperature is 14.16\u00b0C."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temperature/weather today(04-08-2024) in Naivasha?",
        "answer": "The weather today (04-08-2024) in Naivasha will see a low of 14.66\u00b0C and a high of 14.66\u00b0C, with broken clouds. The average temperature is 14.66\u00b0C. Morning temperature is 14.66\u00b0C, evening temperature is 14.66\u00b0C, and night temperature is 14.66\u00b0C."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temperature/weather today(04-08-2024) in Malindi?",
        "answer": "The weather today (04-08-2024) in Malindi will see a low of 23.29\u00b0C and a high of 23.29\u00b0C, with light rain. The average temperature is 23.29\u00b0C. Morning temperature is 23.29\u00b0C, evening temperature is 23.29\u00b0C, and night temperature is 23.29\u00b0C."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temperature/weather today(04-08-2024) in Kitui?",
        "answer": "The weather today (04-08-2024) in Kitui will see a low of 15.42\u00b0C and a high of 15.42\u00b0C, with broken clouds. The average temperature is 15.42\u00b0C. Morning temperature is 15.42\u00b0C, evening temperature is 15.42\u00b0C, and night temperature is 15.42\u00b0C."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temperature/weather today(04-08-2024) in Kikuyu?",
        "answer": "The weather today (04-08-2024) in Kikuyu will see a low of 14.26\u00b0C and a high of 14.26\u00b0C, with overcast clouds. The average temperature is 14.26\u00b0C. Morning temperature is 14.26\u00b0C, evening temperature is 14.26\u00b0C, and night temperature is 14.26\u00b0C."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temperature/weather today(04-08-2024) in Nakuru?",
        "answer": "The weather today (04-08-2024) in Nakuru will see a low of 12.55\u00b0C and a high of 12.55\u00b0C, with broken clouds. The average temperature is 12.55\u00b0C. Morning temperature is 12.55\u00b0C, evening temperature is 12.55\u00b0C, and night temperature is 12.55\u00b0C."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temperature/weather today(04-08-2024) in Kitale?",
        "answer": "The weather today (04-08-2024) in Kitale will see a low of 12.58\u00b0C and a high of 12.58\u00b0C, with broken clouds. The average temperature is 12.58\u00b0C. Morning temperature is 12.58\u00b0C, evening temperature is 12.58\u00b0C, and night temperature is 12.58\u00b0C."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temperature/weather today(04-08-2024) in Mombasa?",
        "answer": "The weather today (04-08-2024) in Mombasa will see a low of 22.2\u00b0C and a high of 22.2\u00b0C, with broken clouds. The average temperature is 22.2\u00b0C. Morning temperature is 22.2\u00b0C, evening temperature is 22.2\u00b0C, and night temperature is 22.2\u00b0C."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the temperature/weather today(04-08-2024) in Kisumu?",
        "answer": "The weather today (04-08-2024) in Kisumu will see a low of 15.77\u00b0C and a high of 15.77\u00b0C, with clear sky. The average temperature is 15.77\u00b0C. Morning temperature is 15.77\u00b0C, evening temperature is 15.77\u00b0C, and night temperature is 15.77\u00b0C."
    }
]